cassart.co.uk 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Cass Art

Cass Art is committed to delivering the best experience for our customers. As such, we take our responsibilities in looking after your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy explains how We (Cass Art) will collect and use your personal information.

**Contents**

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * Marketing
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Cookies
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us

**What information do we collect about you?**

We collect information about you when you register with us online, browse online, place an order for products or services online, when you register for one of our loyalty schemes (Cass Art Rewards, Cobalt Blue Card, Viridian Card) and buy products in store.  We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions.  Website usage information is collected using cookies.

**How will we use the information about you?**

We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account or loyalty scheme, and if you agree, to e-mail you about products and services we think may be of interest to you.

We work with carefully selected third parties who are responsible for delivering certain functions on our behalf.  These include companies that run our website, process payments, deliver e-mails, deliver orders and manage our loyalty scheme.  When we share personal data with these providers we require them to keep it safe and not keep it for any longer than they need to in order to perform their responsibilities.

We will never share your personal information with anyone for marketing purposes.

**Marketing**

If you have consented to receive marketing we will send you information about products, services and opportunities which might interest you. 

When you register for one of our loyalty schemes (Cass Art Rewards, Colbalt Blue and Viridian Cards) we will collect and process your data, including email address, in order to fulfil the benefits of the scheme.  This will include sending updates on your account to you via email and telling you about relevant exclusive offers and events.

You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any newsletter.

In the interests of monitoring and improving our service, online customers will receive an email from Ekomi asking you to review your experience shopping with us. Should you wish to not receive emails from Ekomi, contact us [by email](https://www.cassart.co.uk/customer/contact).

**Access to your information and correction**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.  If you would like a copy of your personal information please complete this [form](https://www.cassart.co.uk/customer/contact).  We may make a small charge for this service.

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date.  You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a very small piece of information that a website stores to save and collect basic information. Many cookies are essential to the operation of our website, for example to allow you to make a purchase or create an account with us. Cookies on our site are also used to customise certain areas of content just for you, and to make your browsing experience more efficient and faster.

For more information read our [cookie policy](https://www.cassart.co.uk/customer/pages/cookies).

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will update this web page with any changes.  This privacy policy was last updated on 15 May 2018.

**How to contact us**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you;

  * Or write to us at Customer Care, Cass Art, 93 Bayham Street, Camden, London NW1 0AG
